(Penny:)Did you know last weekend
Priya took Leonard
(Penny:)rollerblading
at the beach?
(Penny:)Can you believe that?
(Bernadette:)I feel like I'm supposed
to say "that bitch,"
(Bernadette:)but I don't have
enough information.
(Penny:)I am the one who
spent two years
(Penny:)trying to get him to even
(Penny:)go to the beach
in the first place.
(Penny:)And he was so phobic about
stepping on medical waste,
(Penny:)I had to carry him
to the water.
(Bernadette:)I took Howard to the beach once.
(Bernadette:)He almost burst into flames
like a vampire.
(Penny:)So what's the thanks
I get for turning Leonard
(Penny:)into quality boyfriend material?
(Penny:)I have to tiptoe around
his new girlfriend.
(Amy:)I think you're on.
Oh.
(Bernadette:)That bitch!
(Penny:)Want some coffee liqueur
on your ice cream?
(Amy:)Ah, here's the alcohol
and drug peer pressure
(Amy:)Mother warned me about.
(Amy:)I was starting to think
it was never going to happen.
(Amy:)Yes, please.
(Penny:)You guys should've seen Leonard
when I first met him.
(Penny:)There was no eye contact.
(Penny:)He was either looking
up at the ceiling,